[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of seafood is used in the making of the Korean salad Golbaengi muchim?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Squid", "Fish", "Sea snails"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The first transcontinental car trip, S.F. to NYC, was made in 1906. How long did it take?", "correct_answer": "52  days", "incorrect_answers": ["5 weeks", "2 weeks", "52 hours"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the unusual name of the character played by actress Gina Gershon in the movie Cocktail?", "correct_answer": "Coral", "incorrect_answers": ["Ruby", "Opal", "Jade"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which statement is true about John Larroquettes birth?", "correct_answer": "He was  born  11/25/1947 in New Orleans", "incorrect_answers": ["He was born 11/23/1952 in Boston", "He was  born 11/24/1957 in Chicago", "He was born 11/26/1962 in  Providence"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What notable feature does the Gentoo Penguin possess which makes it easily recognizable?", "correct_answer": "A white stripe on the top of its head", "incorrect_answers": ["A longer blue tail", "A red crest on its head", "A yellow spot on its abdomen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which sport is mentioned in Shakespeares Henry V?", "correct_answer": "Tennis", "incorrect_answers": ["Golf", "Bowling", "Darts"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What record label was established in 1978 and included New Order, The Durutti Column and Happy Mondays in its stable?", "correct_answer": "Factory Records", "incorrect_answers": ["Fall records", "Fire Records", "Fiction records"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Leonardo Da Vinci made a series of still pictures that showed motion, when flipped.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actress starred in the 1993 movie Flesh and Bone, also featuring Dennis Quaid, James Caan and Gwyneth Paltrow?", "correct_answer": "Meg Ryan", "incorrect_answers": ["Melanie Griffith", "Uma Thurman", "Heather Graham"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1985 movie is this quote from: Holy jumped up bald-headed Jesus palomina. From him Id expect it. Sometimes I think your common sense got paralyzed along with your legs. But from you Jane??", "correct_answer": "Silver Bullet", "incorrect_answers": ["Re-Animator", "The Return of the Living Dead", "Pumpkinhead"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What defense method do ostriches use when they are attacked or feel threatened?", "correct_answer": "Kicking", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "They bury their heads in the sand.", "They use their wings to beat the enemy."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these actors did not appear in the 1993 movie The Fugitive?", "correct_answer": "Jack Nicholson", "incorrect_answers": ["Harrison Ford", "Tommy Lee Jones", "Julianne Moore"]}]